Elliana Gang

www.linkedin.com/in/ellianagang16

Current Senior at University of California, San Diego (UCSD) pursuing a Bachelor's degree in Cognitive Science with a Specialization in Design and Interaction. Demonstrates a clear understanding in design, user research, user interface, hospitality, customer service, and communications. Thrives on transforming intricate problems into aesthetically pleasing yet user-friendly solutions that not only look amazing but also are efficient and user-based. Exhibits this by combining the foundations in design principles and user psychology with a meticulousness for details, striving to help solve any problem,

EXPERIENCE

Aritzia, San Diego, CA / Inventory Associate

AUG 2023 - NOV 2023 / www.artizia.com

Provided support with the movement of merchandise into and out of the store, while contributing to seamless operations in all aspects of the retail space.

Abercrombie and Fitch, San Diego, CA / Brand Ambassador

FEB 2022 - JUL 2022 / www.abercrombie.com

Provided customer service and worked in various areas in the store including inventory, register, fitting rooms, and organization.

ArtPower, San Diego, CA / Production Assistant

JAN 2022 - FEB 2022 /artpower.ucsd.edu

Duties include: transporting materials, props, equipment, and performers. Lifting, moving, and setting up the stage. Assisting the production manager in running the event.

INTERNSHIP

UI/UX Team, Seodaemun-gu, Seoul, Korea / Intern

AUG 2023 -DEC 2023

Interned under Professor Ted Yoo at Yonsei University as a part of the UCEAP internship program. The company I worked for was Vrillar, a distinguished company specializing in video reality and augmented reality content, I was immersed in the creation of high-quality content spanning three main categories: VR/AR games, VR educational software, and VR visualization. Vrillar's noteworthy project, ME.RROR, stands as a testament to its commitment to introducing diverse Asian assets to the 3D realm.

8950 Costa Verde Blvd Apt 4131 San Diego, CA 92122 (714-319-3917) egang@ucsd.edu

TOOLBOX

Figma, HTML, ATOM, JavaScript, Word, PowerPoint, Excel, Google Suite, Python, C++, Adobe Indesign, Inkscape

ACTIVITIES

Campus Outreach

Coordinated weekly and quarterly events for campus club as a part of the leadership team.

Redeemer Presbyterian Church

Served as a teaching assistant at the children ministry.

Generation of Daughters

Run social media, shopify, and marketing for a jewelry brand.

LANGUAGES

English

EDUCATION

UC San Diego, La Jolla, CA / Design and Interaction BS

OCT 2020 - DEC 2024

Yonsei University, Seoul, South Korea

AUG 2023-DEC 2023